{
    "id": "e7693e08b94a4043bef8124b74a1400e",
    "title": "Prepositions Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "You must abide ……………………. the laws.",
            "description": "Abide is followed by ‘by’.",
            "answers": [
                "with",
                "by",
                "on"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "83d39fc14b5b4a28aba1ad68332bb786"
        },
        {
            "question": "This pond abounds ………………….. fish.",
            "description": "Abound can be followed by in/with. ",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "with",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "30a26f3052ef44ccbb29e0da9fb6649c"
        },
        {
            "question": "I didn’t see him because I was absorbed …………………. my work.",
            "description": "If you are absorbed in something, its holds your attention of.",
            "answers": [
                "with",
                "in",
                "on"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "75679c351b394d1da1109502c9bb9adc"
        },
        {
            "question": "We tried our best to accommodate …………………….. their needs.",
            "description": "There is no preposition after accommodate",
            "answers": [
                "to",
                "with",
                "No preposition is required"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "48ce9451113540498d88cc1ccef7dde9"
        },
        {
            "question": "Money was …………………… no account to them.",
            "description": "If something is of no account to you, it is not important for you.",
            "answers": [
                "for",
                "of",
                "on"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "5d7444eecdda43ca8141a0aa643cb4c9"
        },
        {
            "question": "He was accused ……………………… murdering his landlord.",
            "description": "Accused is followed by of.",
            "answers": [
                "with",
                "of",
                "over"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "4ca4c3571acb47fd88e0b56796f3186c"
        },
        {
            "question": "All members must adhere …………………… a code of conduct.",
            "description": "Adhere is followed by to.",
            "answers": [
                "to",
                "with",
                "for"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "9d9f10c1b89f4e8bb0134085e6c79294"
        },
        {
            "question": "His body language did not agree ………………… what he was saying.",
            "description": "Agree with means be consistent with.",
            "answers": [
                "on",
                "with",
                "to"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "17e50da6d0744e89bfe5960f74f1fd93"
        },
        {
            "question": "The manager did not agree …………………… my leaving early.",
            "description": "To agree to something is to consent to it.",
            "answers": [
                "with",
                "to",
                "on"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "cda9ea385ddc4e49b695f770013c8d9c"
        },
        {
            "question": "It was a lifestyle that was completely alien ………………….. me.",
            "description": "If something is alien to you, it is not acceptable to you.",
            "answers": [
                "for",
                "to",
                "with"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "edc22e988e4c477894d19c407f6d0a3d"
        },
        {
            "question": "Would you mind if I brought ……………………. a few friends?",
            "description": "To bring along a few friends is to bring them with you.",
            "answers": [
                "up",
                "over",
                "along"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "f01f1dd2716e4466bb0239e2f6a7c3e4"
        },
        {
            "question": "I had lost my appetite …………………… study.",
            "description": "Appetite for means a liking.",
            "answers": [
                "to",
                "for"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "a0e9fa81449f4d05a178a3efe4388424"
        }
    ]
}